playomg.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

PlayOMG maintains this Privacy Policy ("Policy") that summarizes our policies and processes for protecting the privacy of all personal information gathered from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our website(s) or who download PlayOMG's products and services, and when and how such information is collected, used, and safeguarded. This Policy also explains how anyone can review, update, correct, or delete their personal information and specify what information, if any, they would like to receive from PlayOMG on an on-going basis.

**● Introduction**  
PlayOMG is committed to ensuring your privacy and protecting the security of your personal information. This Policy covers the public PlayOMG websites - http://member.en.playomg.com— and all online forms on the Website used to collect personal information. Please note that this Policy applies only to sites maintained by PlayOMG or its affiliates, and not third party sites, whether linked to or from the Website. Moreover, this Policy does not only apply to information collected by PlayOMG offline. In addition, this Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. By using the Website, you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of this Policy and that your use of the Website, including, downloads of any of PlayOMG's products and services, is subject to PlayOMG's Terms of Service. **If you do not agree with any terms or conditions described in this Policy, User’s Agreement, or the Terms of Use, please exit from the Website.**

**● Collecting Personal Information**  
You can access our Website without providing us with any personal information. However, PlayOMG may collect personal information in various locations on our Website as more particularly described below. Our primary goal in collecting the information described below is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Website and to deliver better service, products, and more relevant content to our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. 

**● Personal Information We Collect**  
Personal information may be collected from you during (a) the registration process, (b) promotional campaigns, (c) customer support and technical service requests, and/or (d) ordering of products and other services from the Website or from third party service providers. This information may include your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, birth date, occupation, gender, account ID, passwords, and/or payment and billing information. From time to time we may expand or change the information requested upon registration, so this may not be a complete list. We ask that you provide only your own personal information, not personal information concerning anyone else. Personal information may be collected by PlayOMG and/or business partners such as co-sponsors. 

**● Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We may use cookies to track general, non-personal information about our users (e.g., user name, pages viewed, time spent our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our Website) for statistical and market research purposes. The information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis. 

We use cookies to gather information about our Website users' browser activities in order to constantly improve our Website and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in a most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Website to better meet the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. 

You have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the option to reject all cookies, which may, however, in limited instances prevent you from accessing certain features on our Website. 

**● Log Files**  
Like most Internet services, we may also use log files on the server side. The data held in log files includes your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, e-mail application, Internet service provider, referring/exit Web pages, computer platform type, date/time stamp, and user activity (e.g., feature usage, user rankings, game statistics). PlayOMG uses server log data to analyze trends, administer the services offered through the Website. IP addresses are not tied to any personally identifiable information.

The software enabling the Website has associated log and temporary files that are stored on PlayOMG's servers. These files store your account information, preference settings, system notifications as well as other data necessary to enable you to participate on the Website. Your information may also exist within regularly performed server backups.

The foregoing information is collected on an aggregated and anonymous basis. 

**● Monitoring/Public Information**  
When any game is updated or "patched," our patch routine may check your computer to see that you have the most recent version of game-specific files; when you communicate within any game or any other communication feature within the game (e.g., live chat, instant message services and the like), even "privately" to another person, you do so with the understanding that those communications go through our servers, can be monitored by us, you have no expectation of privacy in any of those communications and, accordingly, you expressly consent to monitoring of communications that you send and receive.

You may also choose to disclose personal information in our online chat rooms, blogs, bulletin boards, and other public forums made available through the Website. Personal information you disclose in such public forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality. Please refer to the Terms of Service for additional information relating to the disclosure of personal information on public forums.

**● Use of Personal Information**  
Unless otherwise described elsewhere in this Policy, or under the Users Agreement, we will not disclose any personal information collected from customers, prospective customers, or visitors.

**● Use by PlayOMG**  
We use the information you provide so that we may better understand the needs of our customers, prospective customers, and visitors. Specifically, we use your personal information for many purposes, including:

  1. to allow you to register to use our products and services; 
  2. to ensure the continued smooth operation of our service; 
  3. to communicate with you concerning your account or to send you newsletters, surveys, contest announcements, and information about our service or product offerings or the offerings of our business partners; 
  4. to prevent or investigate actual or suspected fraud, hacking, infringement, or other misconduct involving our products and services, or this Website; 
  5. to respond to inquiries, troubleshoot problems, investigate incidents, and handle complaints; and 
  6. to develop to new products and services. 

**● Sharing with Business Partners**  
We generally do not sell or trade any personal information about our customers, prospects, or visitors to any third parties. We may share, however, aggregated demographic information with our business partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We may also periodically engage in co-marketing activities, where we work with a complementary solution provider to launch a joint marketing program. In these situations, we will only send information to you on behalf of the other; we do not provide your personal information to such partner. We may also enter into business partnerships with other parties to provide specific services. If a user signs up for these services or responds to a particular marketing offer, we may share personal information such as your name or other contact information that is necessary for our business partner to provide these services or get in contact with you.

Finally, in the event PlayOMG combines with another company in the future through a corporate merger, sale, acquisition, liquidation or other similar process, your personal information may be transferred with the business or a part of it, or may be sold as an asset of the business.

PlayOMG may also share information with its parent (Macrowell OMG Group) or subsidiaries. In case of legal issues, it may share information by court order, with enforcement agencies, or with consultants or companies it may hire related to the matter. In such cases they will be required to abide by PlayOMG’s privacy rules and keep all information confidential.

**● Storage of Personal Information and Security**  
We take reasonable precaution to protect the personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors. When users submit personal information via the Website, the information is housed in a secure in-house database. To prevent unauthorized access, loss, or misuse, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the personal information we maintain. PlayOMG uses industry-standard technology, such as firewalls, in an effort to protect the confidentiality of your personal information. Moreover, we encrypt your transmission of sensitive information to us (e.g., account passwords and payment-related identifiable information) via SSL (secured socket layer) protocol in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity. 

In addition, only employees who need the information to perform their duties are granted access to personally identifiable information. The unauthorized access or use of such information by an employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access.

Furthermore, our trusted vendors and business partners are responsible for processing or handling some of the information that we receive. These vendors and business partners are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information. 

However, while we strive to protect your personal information, you should know that information sent over the Internet, whether by e-mail or by using one of our on-line forms, is not necessarily secure against interception. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for such interception and cannot guarantee the security of such information.

**● Opt-Out Provision**   
When we first collect information from you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of PlayOMG (unless otherwise described in this Policy). In addition, if you do not want PlayOMG to send you e-mail or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt-out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name or any other personal information removed from our mailing list, you can do so by going here and filling in the request form.

**● Review, Update, Correct, or Delete Personal Information**  
Generally, you may review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected by the Website. You may also correct factual inaccuracies. Certain types of personal information that is necessary to check eligibility, such as birth date or age, cannot be deleted, but may be modified with sufficient verification of the new information. Note that we reserve the right to terminate or delete any registration or promotional entry if we believe the personal information submitted was knowingly false or fraudulent. 

To review, update, correct or delete your personal information collected by   
the Website, please go here.

To have access to your personal information, you must provide proof of identification such as full name, street address, city/state and zip code, user ID and password, and/or information about your recent activity on the Website. We reserve the right to deny access to any user if we believe there is a question about your identity. And if the burden or expense of providing access to your personal information is disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or if the legitimate rights of others would be violated, we may decide not to provide access to such information. Moreover, we may still retain your information in our files to resolve disputes, enforce the Terms of Service, and for technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the Website. 

**● Legal Disclaimer**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law, regulation, court order, or in response to a subpoena or litigation discovery request, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us. 

**● Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Policy, we will post those changes on our Policy page so you are aware of what personal information we collect from customers, prospective customers, and visitors to our Website, and when and how such information is collected, used and safeguarded. You are responsible for periodically checking our Website for changes to this Policy. If at any time we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will take commercially reasonable measures to obtain e-mail consent from you. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your personal information in this different manner. 

**● No Guarantees**  
While this Policy states our standards for maintenance of personal information and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of personal information. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of any personal information collected from customers, prospective customers, or visitors.

**● Users Outside Taiwan**  
PlayOMG is subsidiary of Macrowell OMG Group, a Taiwan company operating under OMG. OMG's business operations are primarily conducted in Taiwan. We operate our company and administer our policies according to the applicable Taiwan laws and regulations. If you use our service from outside Taiwan, you are thereby consenting for your personal information to be processed in Taiwan in the manner described in this Policy. Furthermore, you acknowledge that the privacy laws of Taiwan may differ from the laws in the country where you are located and may not provide you the same rights or protections as those laws.
